Hello friends, welcome to your YouTube
channel. This is going to be
very important,
so please watch the video till the end.
Friends, we will meet again today with a new vacancy. The
vacancy that has come out today is for
your
recruitment by ICC Bank for the post of PO Clerk and Assistant
Manager. This
vacancy is going to be the best vacancy for you people.
You
can apply for this vacancy from all over India.
Today, through this video, I will
tell you from when to when your forms will be filled, what is the
application fee, what
qualification is
required in it, so
watch the video till the end for complete information. If you have
not liked the video yet, then
like and share it. If you are on the channel for the first
time, then definitely subscribe to the channel. So,
let's start the video by asking
how many vacancies have been announced for your posts.
Your vacancies have been announced for approximately 4000 posts.
Post names in this are
PO Clerk, Assistant Manager, Relationship
Manager and other posts.
Online date for larger means from
when will your applications be filled, so the
application process i.e. the
forms you have have already started filling from 19 October 2022
and
your forms will be filled by 25 November 2022, sorry
here it is October, your
[music]
application
fee is for General OBC, Use S
& F, here almost no
fee has been kept for any candidate, the
forms of all the candidates will be filled absolutely free, if we
talk about the limit then
your minimum age limit should be 18 to maximum 25
years, relaxation will also be seen in the future
like OBC candidates will get
three years of experience, this will be
relaxed in the future and your
pressure candidates who have engine experience can also
apply, freshers can
also apply, this is going to be your
permanent job which is a very
good thing, what should be the qualification for you people, then the
qualification should be your 10th  It is mandatory to be 12th and graduate,
so your selection is your interview
for this, that is, what is going to be your salary,
so your salary is minimum ₹ 20000
to maximum ₹ 45000 per month is being accepted,
how much salary will you get, that is,
your Harman's mount is going to be very good,
your plymoon will be
online, the job location for you is
going to be all of India, that is, if you belong to
any state of India, any city or any
village, you can apply for it,
how did you like the information, do tell us in the comment section,
like the video, share it,
press the bell icon so that our